sachkhabar.com 2018-03-14

# Privacy Policy

Sachkhabar.com respects the privacy of its users and is committed to protect it in all respects. The information about the user as collected by Desi Media Sach Khabar is by two means:

(a) Information supplied by users (b) Information automatically tracked while navigating information

By using sachkhabar.com website or its services, you consent to collection, storage and use of the personal information you provide (including any changes thereto as provided by you) for any of the services that we offer.

**User Information**

To avail certain sites / services on our websites, users may be required to provide certain information for the registration process namely:

(a) You name (b) email address (c) sex (d) age (e) PIN code (f) password (g) your occupation (h) interests etc.

The information as supplied by the users enables us to improve our sites and provide you the most user friendly experience.

All required information is service dependent and sachkhabar.com may use the above said user information to maintain, protect and improve its services (including advertising services) and for developing new services.

Such information will not be considered as sensitive if it is freely available and accessible in the public domain or it furnished under under the right to Information Act, 2005 or any other law for the time being in force.

**Cookies**

Desi Media Sach Khabar includes link to other websites. Such websites are governed by their respective privacy policies, which are beyond our control. Once you leave our servers (you call tell where you are by checking the URL in the location bar on your browser), use of any information you provide governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting. That policy may differ from ours. If you can’t find the privacy policy of any of these sites via a link from the site’s homepage, you should contact the site directly for more information.

Our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer’s connection to the internet, including IP address, when you visit our site. (Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the internet). Your IP address dose not identify you personally. We use this information to deliver our web pages to you upon request, to tailor our site to the interests of our users, to measure traffic withing our site and let advertisers know the geographic locations from where our visitor come.

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit:

**Information Sharing**

Desi Media Sach Khabar shares the sensitive personal information with any third party without obtaining the prior consent of the user in the following limited circumstances:

a: When it is requested or required by law or by any court or government agency or authority to disclose, for the purpose of verification of identity, or for the prevention, detection, investigation including cyber incidents, or for prosecution and punishment of offences. These disclosures are made in good faith and belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary for enforcing these terms; for complying with the applicable laws and regulations.

b: Desi Media Sach Khabar purposes to share such information within its group companies and officers and employees of such group companies for the purpose of processing personal information on its behalf. We also ensures that these recipient of such information agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

**Information Security**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These includes internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to system where we store site data.

All information gathered on sachkhabar.com is securely stored withing the site databases. The databases is stored on servers secured behind a firewall. Access to the server is password protected and is strictly limited. However, as effective as our security measures are, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the internet. And of course, any information you include in posting to the discussion areas is available to anyone with internet access.

However the internet is an ever evolving medium. We may change our privacy policy from time to time to incorporate necessary future changes. Of course our use of any information we gather will always be consistent with the policy under which the information was collected, regardless of what the new policy may be.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including you name, address, email, telephone number) about your visits to this sites and all other sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. In the event you have any grievance relating to the processing of information provided by you, you may contact over phone or write at the following addresses:

2M-44, NIT-2, Faridabad, Pin-121001, Haryana
